{
    "subject": "Tony_Bui",
    "predicate": "produced",
    "object": "Three_Seasons",
    "human_readable": "Tony Bui produced Three Seasons.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9418143630027771,
            "question": "Has Tony Bui won any awards for producing Three Seasons?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6697977781295776,
            "question": "Who produced the movie Three Seasons?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4794894754886627,
            "question": "When was the movie Three Seasons released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4535788893699646,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie produced by Tony Bui?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44746193289756775,
            "question": "Can you name other movies produced by Tony Bui?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4055197834968567,
            "question": "Is Tony Bui a film director or producer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33253514766693115,
            "question": "Who are the main actors in the movie Three Seasons?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31838977336883545,
            "question": "What genre is the movie Three Seasons?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29428818821907043,
            "question": "Where was the movie Three Seasons filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24619971215724945,
            "question": "What is the plot of the movie Three Seasons?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tony Bui produced Three Seasons.",
            "html": "yago_9854_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was the movie Three Seasons filmed?",
            "html": "yago_9854_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the movie Three Seasons?",
            "html": "yago_9854_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the main actors in the movie Three Seasons?",
            "html": "yago_9854_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9854_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9854_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9854_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9854_172.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9854_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9854_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9854_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9854_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9854_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9854_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* Tony Bui is indeed the director of the film \"Three Seasons\".\n* There are multiple mentions of Tony Bui's involvement with the film \"Three Seasons\", but none of them mention him producing it. Instead, Harvey Keitel is credited as executive producer.\n* The context also mentions that Three Seasons was granted permission to be fully shot on Vietnamese grounds, and that Tony Bui left Vietnam with his family at a young age.\n\nGiven this information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Tony Bui directed the film \"Three Seasons,\" which supports the statement that Tony Bui produced it, as producing and directing are closely related roles in filmmaking."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The text explicitly states that Tony Bui directed Three Seasons, but does not mention him as the producer.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}